A passion. An obsession. A love that destroyed everyone it touched.
Wuthering Heights is a drama, romance film directed by Peter Kosminsky.
Young orphan Heathcliff is adopted by the wealthy Earnshaw family
and moves into their estate, Wuthering Heights.
Soon, the new resident falls for his compassionate foster sister, Cathy.
The two share a remarkable bond that seems unbreakable until Cathy, feeling the pressure of social
convention, suppresses her feelings and marries Edgar Linton, a man of means who befits her stature.
Heathcliff vows to win her back.
Cathy / Catherine Linton, played by Juliette Binoche.
Heathcliff, played by Ralph Fiennes.
Ellen Dean, played by Janet McTeer.
Isabella Linton, played by Sophie Ward.
Edgar Linton, played by Simon Shepherd.
Hindley Earnshaw, played by Jeremy Northam.
Emily Brontë's Wuthering Heights is a 1992 historical film adaptation of Emily
Brontë's 1847 novel Wuthering Heights directed by Peter Kosminsky.
It marked Ralph Fiennes's film debut.
This particular film is notable for including the oft-omitted second
generation story of the children of Cathy, Hindley and Heathcliff.
The tone is emotional.